ppfinder.com 2017-12-01

# People search - Find people over the internet for free - White Pages

## Privacy Policy

Ppfinder.com has developed this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to maintaining the privacy of the information that you provide when using Ppfinder.com application. Our site also uses data from publicly accessible sources like from third party public data suppliers. As a consumer, you have the ability to make certain choices on the Ppfinder.com website that will govern how Ppfinder.com will handle your personal information and provide you with control over how Ppfinder.com shares that information.

This privacy policy explains the source of site information and how specific information is protected, collected and used by Ppfinder.com. This policy may be occasionally updated by Ppfinder.com. Ppfinder.com will, however, provide notice of significant changes to this privacy policy by posting a notice on the Ppfinder.com web site.

In Ppfinder.com account settings, you can remove certain information on Ppfinder.com completely from the public eye. However, information is updated daily. Control of information obtained from publicly accessible external sources is beyond our control as billions of records are updated monthly. Please contact these sources directly to remove certain information.

By submitting personal information to the Ppfinder.com web site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your personal information according to this Privacy Policy.

1\. SITE INFORMATION SOURCE.

Ppfinder.com searches only publicly available sources information. If the information that we show is outdated we encourage users to correct that data at the original source or by sending us a document showing the correct information and we will update it. 

It is important for you to understand that we acquire much of the information published on our websites from publicly available sources, third-party data suppliers and other sources. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to that information. It applies only to the information that you provide directly to us.

2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU.

Ppfinder.com collects profile data, including, but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education, connections with other people or communities, and occupation, in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

Ppfinder.com provides a platform for sharing of information by people about people. Such information can include personal reviews, praises, endorsement, interests, suggestions and other related information. Such information is considered public and is made available to general public only per publishing user's explicit consent at the time of such posting.

Ppfinder.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

3\. COOKIES.

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information submitted on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

4\. CHILDREN.

Ppfinder.com prohibits using of its web site for people under the age 18. Ppfinder.com makes all efforts possible in preventing collection of personal information about children under age 18.

DISCLOSURE.

ALTHOUGH WE MAKE EVERY ATTEMPT POSSIBLE TO KEEP THE INFORMATION AS SECURE AS POSSIBLE, Ppfinder.com IS NOT COMPLETELY IMMUNE TO SECURITY BREACHES AND UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS. WE CANNOT GUARANTEE YOU COMPLETE PROTECTION OF YOUR CONTENT. WE URGE YOU TO BE CONSCIOUS ABOUT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU ARE SHARING.

CONTACT US:

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the "contact us" form on the Ppfinder.com web site.
